全球超过15亿人，超过一半的人口在24岁以下，每天都会观看短视频，长度不超过60秒，使用Snapchat、TikTok、Instagram Stories等智能手机应用。
More than 1.5 billion people around the world, over half of them under the age of 24, regularly watch short videos, clips of 60 seconds or less, using Snapchat, TikTok, Instagram Stories and other smartphone apps.
七年前这个市场几乎不存在。
The market barely existed seven years ago.
然而，如今，创作者每天上传7002万个短视频。
Yet today, creators are uploading 702 million short videos every day.
随着我们的注意力持续时间降低到秒级，短视频不仅会持续存在，还将成为新常态。
As our attention span is falling to seconds, short video is not only here to stay, but will become the new normal.
与其他社交平台如Instagram不同，那里要求精美编辑的图片是常态，而短视频更具可及性，允许存在缺陷和真实感。
Unlike other social platforms such as Instagram, where perfectly edited, polished images are the norm, short videos are more accessible, inviting imperfection and authenticity.
而因为每个视频片段都很短，因此内容制作人必须具有创造力和简洁的沟通能力。
And because each clip is so short, content producers have to be creative and concise communicators.
但这些小块式视频不仅仅是娱乐，它还有更深层次的意义。
But these bite-sized videos are more than just fun and entertainment.
对我来说作为一名顾问和母亲，短视频是我获取育儿建议的地方。
For me personally, as a consultant and mother, short videos are where I get parenting tips.
上班路上，我可以快速学习如何在旅行中哺乳的秘密，获取让女儿早点睡觉的好想法。
On my way to work, I can quickly learn about the secrets of breastfeeding while traveling and get great ideas about how to make my daughter sleep sooner.
企业也学到了一条重要经验：短视频是找到新客户和扩大观众群的有效方式。
Businesses are also learning that short videos is a great way to find new customers and expand the diversity of the audiences.
今年早些时候，我与全球领先的短视频平台TikTok合作，评估了这种“小块式经济”的经济和社会影响。
Earlier this year, I led a project with TikTok, the world's leading short video platform, to assess the economic and social impact of this bite-sized economy.
我们的研究表明，这种年轻的媒体正在改变我们生活方式远远超过仅仅是消遣时间的方式。
Our study shows that this young medium is changing a lot more than the way we spend our leisure time.
2019年，短视频创造了约950亿美元的商品和服务销售额，全球创造了大约120万个工作岗位。
In 2019, short video generated an estimated 95 billion US dollars in goods and services sold and created roughly 1.2 million jobs globally.
即使在这种短暂的生命中，短视频已经开始影响我们工作、沟通和学习的方式。
Even within this short lifespan, short video is already impacting the way we work, communicate and learn.
在COVID-19时代，世界各地的大多数博物馆面临着无限期的关闭，而许多博物馆迅速行动起来，通过远程方式吸引并参与新一代年轻观众。
In the age of COVID-19, while museums around the world are facing indefinite closure, many have acted quickly to bring in and engage a new, younger audience remotely.
佛罗伦萨的乌菲兹美术馆，三年前刚成立了官方新网站，现在正在使用短视频吸引观众来参观他们的雕像和绘画作品。
The Uffizi Gallery in Florence, which just established its official new website three years ago, is using short video to attract new audiences to their statues and paintings.
通过展览展示Emoji、音乐歌词或幽默的引用。
mit Exhibitionen mit Emojis, Musik-Lyrics oder lustigen Quoten.
博物馆通过这样做使其艺术作品更加多样化和相关，吸引了年轻一代的艺术爱好者。
Das Museum macht sein Kunstwerk mehr abwechslungsvoll und relevant für die junge Generation der Kunstverliebten.
在博物馆的最后一条帖子中，一幅卡通风暴病毒被转化为石头，中间插入了卡拉瓦乔画作中的美杜莎，她有力量改变那些注视她的观众。
In einem ihrer letzten Posts wurde ein Cartoon-Coronavirus in einen Stein gedreht und in der Mitte von Caravaggio-Bildern Medusa zerstört, die die Macht hat, diejenigen zu verändern, die an ihr in Stein blicken.
乌菲兹美术馆还在短视频平台上进行了影响者直播，通过这种方式，让全球观众体验到他们从未亲眼见过的艺术作品。
Uffizi experimentierte auch mit Influencers-Livestreams von der Galerie auf der Short-Video-Plattform, um die Zuschauer weltweit die Kunst zu erleben, die sie nie in Person gesehen haben konnten.
自2020年4月在TikTok上出现以来，博物馆的账号仅仅三个月内就吸引了超过43,000名关注者。
Since its appearance on TikTok in April 2020, the museum's profile has attracted more than 43,000 followers in three months.
与在Twitter上建立的四年时间相比，博物馆在TikTok上的速度远快得多，它在过去四年里也积累了类似的粉丝基础。
The speed is far quicker than their journey on Twitter, where it built up a similar number of fanbases during the past four years.
小企业也正在使用短视频来寻找那些可能从未听说过他们或他们产品的人群。
Small Businesses are also using short video as a way to find new audiences who might have never heard of them or their products before.
2018年，中国领先的短视频平台抖音，以其社会责任倡议的一部分来缓解中国贫困问题，启动了一项帮助中国山区个体农民和小企业销售农产品的活动。
In 2018, Douyin, the leading Chinese short video platform, as part of its social responsibility initiative to alleviate poverty in China, launched a campaign to help individual farmers and small businesses in China's mountainous areas sell farm produce.
作为其试点项目的一部分，抖音邀请内容制作人创作四个15秒的短视频，让观众看到他们产品的质量。
As one of its pilot projects, Douyin invited content producers to create four pieces of 15-second short videos, showcasing the quality of their products.
此外，还有其他常规公关活动，如推广文章等。
This is on top of other regular PR initiatives such as promotional articles.
抖音想利用短视频的巨大用户群来找到对这些产品感兴趣的客户，然后将它们连接到电子商务网站上，让人们可以在观看视频时购买所看到的商品。
Douyin wollte die große User-Base von Short-Videos anbieten, um die Kunden zu finden, die sich auf diese Produkte interessieren, und dann hat sie sie mit der E-Commerce-Website verbunden, damit die Leute Dinge kaufen können, wenn sie die Videos anschauen.
仅仅在五天内，这项倡议已经帮助四千多户家庭在四川省出售了12万公斤肉类。
In nur fünf Tagen hat die Initiative fast 4.000 Familien in der Sichuaner Provinz unterstützt, 120.000 Kilogramm Plumpen zu verkaufen.
许多品牌出于对年轻人的兴趣，利用短视频作为一种新颖的方式来与Generation Z进行互动。
Viele Brands, die sich interessieren, junge Leute zu hirten und zu rekrutieren, haben Short Video als frische Art und Weise genutzt, sich mit Generation Z zu engagieren.
例如，麦当劳的客户中超过一半都是16到24岁之间的人群。
Zum Beispiel sind mehr als die Hälfte von McDonald's-Anbietern zwischen 16 und 24 Jahre alt.
在澳大利亚，这个品牌近年来一直难以招募新员工。
In Australia, the brand was struggling to recruit in recent years.
因此，这个品牌推出了一个名为“Snaplication”的项目，它是一个Snapchat-镜头，可以让用户通过10秒的视频解释为什么自己会是麦当劳理想的员工，然后将他们指向求职申请的链接。
So it launched something called Snaplication, which is a Snapchat-Lens that enabled users to shoot 10-second videos explaining why they'd be a perfect McDonald's employee and then prompt them to the link of job application.
该活动发布后仅24小时内，麦当劳就收到了3000个Snaplication。
Within 24 hours after launching the campaign, McDonald's received 3,000 Snaplications.
这比他们在整个周内通过传统方法获得的四倍多。
viermal mehr als die Anzahl, die sie in der ganzen Woche mit traditionellen Methoden erhielt.
是否使用短视频来招聘是找到合适的人选还是获得人才的最好方式，尚不清楚。
Es ist unklar, ob das Hören über kurzes Video der beste Weg ist, um die richtigen Leute für den Job zu finden oder um Talent zu erhalten.
尽管在招募人数方面可能存在疑问，但这次活动在全球范围内却取得了巨大的成功。
Aber abgesehen von Rekrutierungsnummern war die Kampagne ein globaler Hit.
在沙特阿拉伯，麦当劳在24小时内收到了43000个Snaplication申请。
In Saudi-Arabien hat McDonald's 43.000 Snap-Applikationen in 24 Stunden erhoben.
之后，这家公司又在美国重新推出了这次活动。
and the company launched the campaign again later in the US.
就像我喜欢从短视频中获取育儿建议一样，很多用户也想利用这个平台学习，但是在小块的形式中。
Much like how I like to get parenting tips from short video, many users also want to leverage the platform to learn, but in tiny bite-sized doses.
在我们的研究中，全球短视频用户将该平台最大的好处排名为发现新兴趣和学习新技能。
In our study, short video users globally rank the top benefits of the platform as discovering new interests and learning new skills.
尤其是在新兴市场，短视频对于学习教育具有巨大的潜力，可以改变现状。
In emergent market especially, short video for learning and education has huge potential to change the status quo.
2019年，TikTok在印度启动了一项活动，以民主化印度的数字社群为目标。
In 2019 hat TikTok eine Kampagne in Indien gegründet, mit dem Ziel, die indischen digitalen Gemeinschaften zu demokratisieren.
自从2020年7月以来，TikTok在这些国家仍然存在，并且已经创建了一个很大的需求——教育性短视频内容。
Während die App seit Juli 2020 in den Ländern geblieben ist, hat sie eine große Anforderung für edukationelle Kurzvideocontent gegründet.
而其他平台也开始填补这个空白。
Und andere Plattformen fangen an, den Raum zu füllen.
通过与印度的社交企业、教育初创公司和受欢迎的内容创作者合作，TikTok能够推动这一趋势，生产了涵盖从学校科学到学习新语言等多个主题的15秒短视频。
TikTok was able to spark this trend by collaborating with Indian social enterprises, education startups and popular creators to produce 15-second short videos that cover a range of topics, from school-level science to learning new languages.
随着第一波短视频在平台上广泛传播，观众们开始受到启发。
As the first wave of short video became widely spread on the platform, audiences got inspired.
甚至有些人开始创作自己的教育性内容。
And some even began to create their own educational content.
到2019年10月，活动已经产生了超过1亿个视频，并获得了4800亿次观看。
By October 2019, the campaign had generated more than 10 million videos and garnered 48 billion views.
通过帮助人们学习和参与内容创作的过程，短视频实际上正在帮助培养并训练能够应对未来挑战的专业人士。
Through helping people learn and participate into the process of content creation, short videos are in fact helping prep and train the skilled population that can take on the challenges of the future.
就像所有社交媒体一样，短视频平台也存在着一些合理的关切。
Like all social media, there are valid concerns around short video platforms.
包括数据隐私问题、这种格式的成瘾性以及内容中缺乏细微差别和背景等问题。
including data privacy, the addictive nature of the format and the lack of nuance and context in the content.
然而，我仍然认为短视频的积极方面将会超过其缺点。
However, I still think that the positive outcomes of short video will outweigh its downsides.
我相信，短视频在未来将成为一个更具重要性的经济和社会力量。
I believe short video will become a more vital economic and social force in the future.
正是因为如此，我们需要找到一种正确的方式，通过用户、平台和政策制定者的合作来从这个年轻媒体中获益。
It is precisely because of this that we need to find the right way to benefit from this young medium through collaboration among users, platforms and policy makers.
感谢。
Thank you.